Guide to the Beyond the Pale Records TAM.718
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Israel Defense Forces (IDF) March 9 Demonstration; David Biale on "Size Doesn't Matter" Video; Jodi Jacobson on Stupall-Pitts Fallout; Chip Berlet on Return of the Militias, 2010-03-14; cuid35985 (Box 20, Item 718_0919)
- "Size Doesn't Matter" Video; IDF Demonstration; Stupak Ad, 2010-03-14; cuid35986 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_386)
- March 9 Demonstration at Friends of the IDF Dinner; David Biale on "Size Doesn't Matter" Video; Jodi Jacobson on Stupak Blowback; Chip Berlet on Resurgence of Right-Wing Militias and Populist Rebellion, 2010-03-14; cuid35987 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_452)
- Dubai Killing of Hamas Leader Mahmoud al-Mabhouh, Al-Jazeera Report on Reaction in Israel (Excerpts), 2010-03-21; cuid35988 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_396)
- Josh Blumenthal on Lawfare Conference with Josh Nathan-Kazis; Alan Levine on Debbie Almontaser Equal Employment Opportunity Commission Ruling; Ayman Mohyeldin on Dubai Killing, 2010-03-21; cuid35989 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_453)
- Steve Krubiner on J Street and Knesset Investigation; Christian Parenti on Nuclear Catastrophe in Japan; Jeff Sharlet on C Street: The Fundamentalist Threat to American Democracy, 2010-03-27; cuid35990 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_406)
- Alisa Solomon on Passover Music; Hanna Siniora on Simon Wiesenthal Center's Plans for a Museum of Tolerance on the Mamilla Cemetery Site in Jerusalem; Lois Uttley on Women and Health Care Bill; Joan Marhi on Passover Food, 2010-03-28; cuid35991 (Box 20, Item 718_0906)
- Hanna Siniora on the Museum of Tolerance in Mamilla, Jerusalem; Lois Uttley on Health Care Bill; Joan Nathan on Food for Passover, 2010-03-28; cuid35992 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_455)
- Cecilie Surasky on Israel-Palestine Conflict; Dana Golan on Breaking the Silence NGO; Felix Moeller and Jessica Jacoby on Harlan: In the Shadow of Jew Süss, March 2010; cuid36943 (Box Electronic Records, Item TW_TAM_718_ER_450)
- Liz Krueger on the New York State Budget; Jeff Halper on Israeli Efforts to Rewrite International Law; Hasia Diner on We Remember with Reverence and Love, 2010-04-04; cuid35993 (Box 20, Item 718_0917)
- We Remember with Reverence and Love American Jews and the Myth of Silence after the Holocaust, 1945-1962, 2010-04-04; cuid35994 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_374)
- Hasia Diner on Her Book We Remember with Reverence and Love American Jews and the Myth of Silence after the Holocaust, 1945-1962, 2010-04-04; cuid35995 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_381)
- Kiera Feldman, Birthright Intro; Jeff Halper, International Law, 2010-04-04; cuid35996 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_401)
- Liz Krueger on NY State Budget; Jeff Halper on Israel's Efforts to Rewrite International Law; Hasia Diner on the Myth of American Jewish Response to the Holocaust, 2010-04-04; cuid35997 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_454)
- Birthright Chronicles: "The Bedouin Desert Village Experience," Parts 1 and 2, 2010 April 8; 2010 June 13; cuid35998 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_375)
- Cecilie Surasky on Anat Kamm and Divestment; Richard Kim and Frances Fox Piven on Cloward-Piven Controversy; Seth Wessler and Aine Duggan on Welfare, 2010-04-11; cuid35999 (Box 20, Item 718_0916)
- Cecilie Surasky on Berkeley and American Israel Public Affairs Committee (AIPAC), Anat Kamm; Richard Kim and Frances Fox Piven on Cloward/Piven Conspiracy; Áine Duggan and Seth Wessler on Poverty, Food Security, and Welfare, 2010-04-11; cuid36000 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_445)
- AIPAC and Berkeley [2015-010], circa 2010-04-11; cuid36001 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_603)
- Budrus: Spielman 1, Iltizam Morrar, Spielman 2; Barbara Hogan of South Africa, 2010-04-18; cuid36002 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_365)
- Ronit Avni on Budrus; Kiera Feldman Reporting on Birthright Chronicles 1; Connie Field on Have You Heard from Johannesburg?, 2010-04-18; cuid36003 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_444)
- Max Blumenthal Demo, 2010-04-25; cuid36004 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_403)
- Jenny Romaine with David Buchbinder, 2010-04-25; cuid36005 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_442)
- Petra Bartosiewicz on Syed Fahad Hashmi Case; Josh Nathan-Kazis on Department of Education and Anti-Semitism on Campuses; Max Ajl in Gaza with Updates on Local Conditions, 2010-05-02; cuid36006 (Box 20, Item 718_0902)
- Petra Bartosiewicz on Syed Fahad Hashmi case; Josh Nathan-Kazis on Department of Education and Anti-Semitism on Campuses; Max Ajl Reporting from Gaza, 2010-05-02; cuid36007 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_443)
- Nadia Hijab on Palestinian Roads; Cecilie Surasky on Developments in Israel's Campaign Against Dissenters; Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz Interviews Joyce Antler on Study of the Jewish Mother Image, 2010-05-09; cuid36008 (Box 20, Item 718_0907)
- Nadia Hijab on Palestinian Roads; Cecilie Surasky on Developments in Israel's Campaign Against Dissenters; Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz Interviews Joyce Antler on Study of the Jewish Mother Image, 2010-05-09; cuid36009 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_441)
- Sasha Polakow-Suransky on The Unspoken Alliance: Israel's Secret Relationship with Apartheid South Africa; Huwaida Arraf on Israeli Navy's Confrontation with the Free Gaza Flotilla, 2010-06-06; cuid36010 (Box 20, Item 718_0910)
- Marathon: Sasha Polakow-Suransky on The Unspoken Alliance: Israel's Secret Relationship with Apartheid South Africa, Part 1, 2010-06-06; cuid36011 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_378)
- Marathon: Sasha Polakow-Suransky on The Unspoken Alliance: Israel's Secret Relationship with Apartheid South Africa, Part 2, 2010-06-06; cuid36012 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_439)
- Marathon: Sasha Polakow-Suransky on The Unspoken Alliance: Israel's Secret Relationship with Apartheid South Africa; Huwaida Arraf on Gaza Flotilla, Part 2, 2010-06-06; cuid36013 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_440)
- Kiera Feldman on Birthright Chronicles, Part 2, 2010-06-13; cuid36014 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_377)
- Cecilie Surasky, Flotilla Fallout, BDS-Israel Divestment; Helen Thomas; Phyllis Bennis; Birthright 2 with Kiera Feldman, 2010-06-13; cuid36015 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_438)
- Boycott, Divestment, Sanctions (BDS) Panel, 2010-06-15; cuid36016 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_402)
- Brad Lander, 2010-06-20; cuid36017 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_393)
- Brad Lander on NYC/New York State Budget; Richard Silverstein on Israel's Investigation of Flotilla; Pablo Alvarado on Arizona Immigrant Law; Benita Jain of Immigrant Defense Project, 2010-06-20; cuid36018 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_430)
- 6/5/2010 Boycott, Divestment, Sanctions (BDS) Panel: Donna Nevel, Esther Kaplan, Hannah Mermelstein, Kathleen Peratis, Yonatan Shapira, and J.J. Goldberg, 2010-07-04; cuid36019 (Box 20, Item 718_0909)
- 6/5/2010 Boycott, Divestment, Sanctions (BDS) Panel: Donna Nevel, Esther Kaplan, Hannah Mermelstein, Kathleen Peratis, Yonatan Shapira, and J.J. Goldberg, 2010-07-04; cuid36020 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_431)
- Netanyahu Demonstration; Song From the River to the Sea; Chants; Song Keep on Walkin', 2010-07-08; cuid36021 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_400)
- M.J. Rosenberg on Netanyahu/Obama Washington Meeting; Jeffrey Edelstein on the YIVO Encyclopedia of Jews of Eastern Europe; Rabbi Alissa Wise and Jenny Romaine on Ma'yan and the It's Not Fair! Production, 2010-07-11; cuid36022 (Box 20, Item 718_0915)
- Rabbi Alissa Wise, Shoshi Shapiro, and Carolyn Kettig on Theatrical Production, That's Not Fair, 2010-07-11; cuid36023 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_382)
- The YIVO Encyclopedia of Jews in Eastern Europe; Klezmer Dance Tune "Skotshne" from An-ski Ethnographic Expedition; Song from Yiddish Operetta Shulamis; Avrom Goldfadn; Children's Chorus, 2010-07-11; cuid36024 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_399)
- M.J. Rosenberg on Netanyahu/Obama Washington Meeting; Jeffrey Edelstein on the YIVO Encyclopedia of Jews of Eastern Europe; Rabbi Alissa Wise and Jenny Romaine on Ma'yan and the It's Not Fair! Production, 2010-07-11; cuid36025 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_432)
- Judith Shulevitz on Book The Sabbath World: Glimpses of a Different Order of Time, 2010-07-18; cuid36026 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_364)
- Marianne Hirsch and Leo Spitzer on Their Book, Ghosts of Home: The Afterlife of Czernowitz in Jewish History, 2010-07-18; cuid36027 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_383)
- Marianne Hirsch and Leo Spitzer on Their Book, Ghosts of Home: The Afterlife of Czernowitz in Jewish History; Judith Shulevitz on Her Book The Sabbath World: Glimpses of a Different Order of Time, 2010-07-18; cuid36028 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_433)
- Harvey Pekar Interview with Nan Rubin, 2010-07-25; cuid36029 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_385)
- Adina Hoffman on My Happiness Bears No Relation to Happiness: A Poet's Life in the Palestinian Century; Alisa Solomon on Khirbet Khizeh; Nan Rubin with Harvey Pekar, 2010-07-25; cuid36030 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_435)
- Cecilie Surasky on Israel-Palestine Conflict; Larry Cohler-Esses and Josh Nathan-Kazis Reports on Sales of Caterpillar Bulldozers to Israel; Deb Margolin Interview at Premiere of Imagining Madoff, 2010-08-01; cuid36031 (Box 20, Item 718_0911)
- Cecilie Surasky on Israel-Palestine Conflict; Larry Cohler-Esses and Josh Nathan-Kazis Reports on Sales of Caterpillar Bulldozers to Israel; Alisa Solomon with Deb Margolin on Imagining Madoff, 2010-08-01; cuid36032 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_408)
- Cecilie Surasky on Israel-Palestine Conflict; Larry Cohler-Esses and Josh Nathan-Kazis Reports on Sales of Caterpillar Bulldozers to Israel; Alisa Solomon with Deb Margolin on Imagining Madoff, 2010-08-01; cuid36033 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_434)
- Interview with Pardiss Kebriaei, Senior Attorney at Center for Constitutional Rights (Unedited), 2010-08-20; cuid36034 (Box 20, Item 718_0912)
- Amy Spitalnick on Park51; Pardiss Kebriaei on Targeted Assassinations; Yael Hersonski on A Film Unfinished; Andre Schiffrin on Dr. Seuss & Co. Go to War, 2010-08-22; cuid36035 (Box 20, Item 718_0900)
- A Film Unfinished by Yael Hersonski, 2010-08-22; cuid36036 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_384)
- Pardiss on Legal Challenge to Targeted Assassination; Andre Schiffrin on Dr. Seuss & Co. Go to War, 2010-08-22; cuid36037 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_405)
- Amy Spitalnick on Park51; Pardiss Kebriaei Discusses Center for Constitutional Rights-American Civil Liberties Union (CCR-ACLU) Lawsuit on Targeted Assassinations; Yael Hersonski on A Film Unfinished; Andre Schiffrin on Dr. Seuss & Co. Go to War, 2010-08-22; cuid36038 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_437)
- Tuli Kupferberg Cues, 2010-08-29; cuid36039 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_409)
- Tuli Kupferberg Tribute with Abe Velez, 2010-08-29; cuid36040 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_436)
- Esther Kaplan on Mott's Strike in Williamson, NY; Andrew Stettner on Long-Term Unemployment; Sarah Henry on "America's Mayor: John V. Lindsay and the Reinvention of New York" Exhibition, 2010-09-05; cuid36041 (Box 20, Item 718_0921)
- Sarah Henry on America's Mayor: John V. Lindsay and the Reinvention of New York Exhibition, 2010-09-05; cuid36042 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_372)
- Andrew Stettner Interview on Unemployment and Economic Policies, 2010-09-05; cuid36043 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_407)
- Esther Kaplan on Mott's Strike in Williamson, NY; Andrew Stettner on Long-Term Unemployment; Sarah Henry on America's Mayor: John V. Lindsay and the Reinvention of New York Exhibition, 2010-09-05; cuid36044 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_424)
- Moustafa Bayoumi, Susan Lerner, and Debbie Almontaser Discuss the Controversy Over Park 51, the Planned Muslim-American Cultural Center, 2010-09-12; cuid36045 (Box 20, Item 718_0908)
- Moustafa Bayoumi on Muslim-American Life Post-9/11; Susan Lerner on Roles of the Media in the Park 51 Story, 2010-09-12; cuid36046 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_404)
- Moustafa Bayoumi, Susan Lerner, and Debbie Almontaser Discuss the Controversy Over Park 51, the Planned Muslim-American Cultural Center, 2010-09-12; cuid36047 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_425)
- Jenny Romaine with Gaby Cryan of Sukkos Mob and Tannis Kowalchuk, 2010-09-19; cuid36048 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_427)
- Jim Hoberman on Howl, 2010-09-26; cuid36049 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_371)
- Sandra Schulberg and Stephen Rapp on Nuremberg, 2010-09-26; cuid36050 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_376)
- From Nuremberg: Robert Jackson Opening, Robert Jackson Closing, and Sir Hartley Shawcross, 2010-09-26; cuid36051 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_390)
- Cecilie Surasky on Islamophobia, Campuses, Ariel Artists; Sandra Schulberg and Stephen Rapp on Nuremberg; Jim Hoberman on Howl, 2010-09-26; cuid36052 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_426)
- Aircheck, 2010-10-03; cuid36053 (Box 20, Item 718_0904)
- New Production from Talking Band, Part 2; Michel Warschawski on Negotiations Between Israel, Palestine, and the U.S., 2010-10-03; cuid36054 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_379)
- Janet Poppendieck and Kathy Goldman on School Food Program; Nan Rubin at Sukkah City Design Competition, 2010-10-03; cuid36055 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_389)
- Janet Poppendieck and Kathy Goldman on School Food Program; Ellen Maddow on Panic! Euphoria! Blackout Production for Talking Band; Michel Warschawski on Negotiations Between Israel, Palestine, and the U.S.; Nan Rubin at Sukkah City Design Competition, 2010-10-03; cuid36056 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_429)
- Jill Lepore on the Tea Party; Adam Levin on New Book The Instructions; Matan Cohen, 2010-10-10; cuid36057 (Box 20, Item 718_0922)
- Jill Lepore on the Tea Party; Adam Levin on New Book The Instructions, 2010-10-10; cuid36058 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_417)
- Jill Lepore on the Tea Party; Adam Levin on New Book The Instructions; Matan Cohen, 2010-10-10; cuid36059 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_428)
- Joe Sacco on Footnotes in Gaza; Moustafa Bayoumi on Midnight on the Mavi Marmara; Joined by Contributors, Rashid Khalidi and Phil Weiss, 2010-10-17; cuid36060 (Box 20, Item 718_0905)
- Jim Hoberman and Joe Sacco on Footnotes in Gaza, 2010-10-17; cuid36061 (Box 20, Item 718_1010)
- Excerpts from Rashid Khalidi and Phil Weiss's Remarks at 9/28 Reading and Discussion at Alwan Center for the Arts, 2010-10-17; cuid36062 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_391)
- Andre Schiffrin, Joe Sacco, Parts 1 and 2, 2010-10-17; cuid36063 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_394)
- Joe Sacco, 2010-10-17; cuid36064 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_416)
- Marathon: Rashid Khalidi, Phil Weiss, Part 2, 2010-10-17; cuid36065 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_418)
- Marathon: Joe Sacco, Moustafa Bayoumi, Part 1, 2010-10-17; cuid36066 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_419)
- Jenny Romaine, Cantors, 2010-10-30; cuid36067 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_370)
- Cecilie Surasky on Activism, Anti-Israel Groups, BDS Campaign, etc.; Ari Berman on 2010 Midterm Election Results; Tom Robbins on Governor-Elect Cuomo, 2010-11-07; cuid36068 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_420)
- Kiera Feldman and Marissa Brostoff with Liel Leibovitz on Chosen Peoples; Susannah Heschel on New Play Imagining Heschel About Her Father; Matthew Taylor on Activism and Disruption of Prime Minister Netanyahu's Speech, 2010-11-14; cuid36069 (Box 20, Item 718_0923)
- Liel Leibovitz; Matthew Taylor Clip; Biden Clip, 2010-11-14; cuid36070 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_388)
- Kiera Feldman and Marissa Brostoff with Liel Leibovitz on Chosen Peoples; Susannah Heschel on New Play Imagining Heschel About Her Father; Matthew Taylor on Activism and Disruption of Prime Minister Netanyahu's Speech, 2010-11-14; cuid36071 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_421)
- Encore Presentation of Interviews with Andre Schiffrin on Dr. Seuss & Co. Go to War and Joe Sacco on Footnotes in Gaza, 2010-11-21; cuid36072 (Box 20, Item 718_1009)
- Rebroadcast of Interviews: Andre Schiffrin on Dr. Seuss & Co. Go to War and Joe Sacco on Footnotes in Gaza, 2010-11-21; cuid36073 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_422)
- Abel Samuel (Unedited), circa 2010-11-28; cuid36074 (Box 20, Item 718_1012)
- Music Special: Abe Velez with Maria Raducanu, Jeremiah Lockwood, and Samuel R. Thomas, 2010-11-28; cuid36075 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_423)
- Rachel Meeropol on Animal Enterprise Terrorism Act of 2006 (AETA) and Communications Management Units (CMUs) in Federal Prisons; Martha Schwendener on Anselm Kiefer Exhibition; Claude Lanzmann on Shoah, 2010-12-05; cuid36076 (Box 20, Item 718_0903)
- Rachel Meeropol on AETA and CMUs in Federal Prisons; Claude Lanzmann on Shoah, 2010-12-05; cuid36077 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_387)
- Rachel Meeropol on AETA and CMUs; Martha Schwendener on Anselm Kiefer; Claude Lanzmann on Shoah, 2010-12-05; cuid36078 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_411)
- Mark Greif on Hipsters; Michelle Goldberg on Palestinian Nonviolent Resistance; Yoel Bitran on Sabra Hummus at Princeton University, 2010-12-12; cuid36079 (Box 20, Item 718_0918)
- Mark Greif on Hipsters; Michelle Goldberg on Palestinian Nonviolent Resistance; Yoel Bitran on Sabra Hummus at Princeton University, 2010-12-12; cuid36080 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_410)
- Jews in Heavy Metal, 2010-12-18; cuid36081 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_395)
- Cantors, 2010-12-19; cuid36082 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_413)
- Sen. Bernie Sanders Speech; Michelle Goldberg on Glenn Beck's The Puppet Master; Devin Burghart on "Tea Party Nationalism" Report, 2010-12-26; cuid36083 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_412)
- Ben Sales; Diane Ravitch; Alan Levine, 2011-01-02; cuid36084 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_462)
- Editorial on Killing in Bil'in; Ben Sales on Hillel Guidelines; Diane Ravitch, The Death of Life of the Great American School System; Alan Levine Interviews Louis Begley on Why the Dreyfus Affair Matters, 2011-01-02; cuid36085 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_501)
- Jews and Heavy Metal with Jenny Romaine, 2011-01-06; cuid36086 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_495)
- Michel Warschawski (Mikado) on Gaza; Vivian Gornick Interview, 2011-01-08; cuid36087 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_504)
- Richard Breiman, Co-Author of Hitler's Shadow: Nazi War Criminals, U.S. Intelligence, and the Cold War; Phyllis Bennis on Wikileaks State Department Cables on Israel and Gaza; Aviva Weintraub on Highlights of NY Jewish Film Festival, 2011-01-09; cuid36088 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_500)
- Phyllis Bennis on Egypt; Brad Lander on the State of NYC and NY State; Barbara Bowen on Political Firing at Brooklyn College; Mary Boyle on Scalia, Thomas, and Citizens United, 2011-01-30; cuid36089 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_499)
- Saul Alinsky, Parts 1 and 2; Reading Monsignor Patrick J. Malloy; Reading John L. Lewis, 2011-02-06; cuid36090 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_463)
- Saul Alinsky Marathon: Frances Fox Piven, Peter Dreier, Radical: A Portrait of Saul Alinsky with Nicholas von Hoffman, Part 2, 2011-02-06; cuid36091 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_492)
- Saul Alinsky Marathon - Radical: A Portrait of Saul Alinsky with Nicholas von Hoffman, Part 1, 2011-02-06; cuid36092 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_494)
- Labor Rights in Wisconsin; Local Police Training in HandlingTerrorist Threats; Bridgewater Zoning Law Vote Blocks Construction of AlFalah Center; Who Profits and the Boycott, Divestment, and Sanctions Movement, 2011-03-13; cuid36093 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_493)
- Si Kahn Interview; Nan Rubin on 100th Anniversary of Triangle Fire; Songs: What If the Tea Party was Black?, Jasiri X; Brecht, Eisler, Maria Farantouri; Which Side Are You On, Rebel Diaz; Mayn Rue Plats, June Tabor; "Millworker," James Taylor, 2011-03-20; cuid36094 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_369)
- Si Kahn Interview; Nan Rubin Segment on Triangle Fire 100th Anniversary, 2011-03-20; cuid36095 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_490)
- Christian Parent on Implications of Japan Nuclear Crisis; Jeff Sharlet on C Street and Previous Book; Ruchama Marton, 2011-03-27; cuid36096 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_461)
- Rent Stabilization; Goldstone Book; Dan Fishback, 2011-04-03; cuid36097 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_491)
- Cecilie Surasky on Resolution at TIAA-CREF, JVP's Brandeis Chapter, and Pro-Palestinian Activists at University California at Santa Cruz; Jodi Jacobson on Planned Parenthood and Federal Budget; Udi Aloni on Juliano Mer-Khamis's Assassination, 2011-04-10; cuid36098 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_488)
- Udi Aloni on Juliano Mer-Khamis's Assassination, 2011-04-10; cuid36099 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_497)
- Cheburashka; "Chunga-Changa", 2011-04-17; cuid36100 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_457)
- Eve Sicular (Reading Andrew Young), 2011-04-17; cuid36101 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_489)
- Passover Special, 2011-04-17; cuid36102 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_502)
- Jerrold Nadler on Federal Budget; Hella Winston on Child Abuse; Akiva Eldar on Israel/Palestine Letter, 2011-04-24; cuid36103 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_486)
- Mark Harris Remembering Sidney Lumet; Raja Shehadeh on His Book A Rift in Time: Travels with My Ottoman Uncle, 2011-05-01; cuid36104 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_459)
- Daniel Levy on Hamas-Fatah Agreement; Debt Ceiling with Ethan Pollack; Mark Horns on Sidney Lumet, 2011-05-01; cuid36105 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_487)
- Jeffrey Wiesenfeld on Tony Kushner, 2011-05-05; cuid36106 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_458)
- Marathon: Susan Rosenberg on Her Memoir An American Radical, Part 2, 2011-05-15; cuid36107 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_484)
- Marathon: Brad Lander and Brian Jones on Teacher Layoffs; Rebecca Vilkomerson on Israel and U.S. Policies; Ellen Schrecker on Tony Kushner/CUNY, Part 1, 2011-05-15; cuid36108 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_485)
- Liz Krueger on NY State Budget; Raja Shehadeh on A Rift in Time: Travels with My Ottoman Uncle; Obama and Netanyahu Speeches, 2011-06-05; cuid36109 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_482)
- Obama at American Israel Public Affairs Committee (AIPAC); Netanyahu at Congress, 2011-06-05; cuid36110 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_505)